A lot of marketing looks effective until
you measure it. I'm joined by Jasper CMO
L'Oreal Lynch to discuss how Jasper's
campaign with LinkedIn delivered real
measurable impact.
>> [music]
>> Of all the outcomes, which one made you
most confident that Jasper's rebrand was
working?
>> We were able to see tremendous success
with this overall campaign. We were able
to see that qualified leads [music]
surged 226%
but the incredible thing and probably
the answer to your question that we
could see that this was working is that
that happened well the cost per lead was
reduced by 40%. You never see that. You
never [music] see leads go up while the
cost per lead goes down. We're reaching
the right people and so we were getting
quality and at a lower price.
>> In [music] what ways did LinkedIn help
shape perception, not just drive clicks,
especially for a [music] category
redefinition?
>> I think the biggest way LinkedIn helped
to shift perception for us specifically
was by offering that professional
context because a lot of our buyers who
are on LinkedIn are there because they
want to learn [music]
and by giving us a platform to deliver
not just ads but knowledge that's
actually valuable to the people who are
engaging with the Jasper brand and the
Jasper content was really big for us and
helped to drive that perception shift.
For us to be able to put our content out
there not just to drive leads but truly
to educate the market that helped
establish us as a credible thought
leader and LinkedIn gave us a platform
to be able to do that. You know, just
anecdotally without even looking at the
numbers, I can see that it's working
just in terms of the types of responses
that we're getting. I get, you know,
people in my DMs, other marketing
leaders and CMOs they're asking for our
advice, they're asking for our opinions
on what it looks like to roll out good
AI-powered marketing.
>> [music]